Supplementary classes for a month?!
Apparently it was just
decided at a staff meeting.
If there's even one failing grade
on our proficiency tests,
the whole class has to take
supplementary classes!
What?!
That's not good.
What should we do? We're
in a bind, Masamune-kun.
Yeah, we're gonna have to work hard.
I'm sure it'll be easy for you.
Nah. The people who really
have it easy are... well...
They look like him.
You don't look worried at all about
the proficiency test, Kojuurou.
Yeah. We need to work hard.
I only managed single-digit grades
in all subjects on our midterms.
I'm hoping to get double-digit
grades this time.
I had no idea he was that stupid!
Kojuurou-kyun is bound for
the supplementary classes!
If he ends up losing even more weight
and becomes more of a bottom, I...
Hold up. You're into that stuff, Futaba-san?
Well, otokonoko (boys) and otokonoko
(traps) are two different things.
They're the same word, but I can tell you
mean them in totally different ways!
I don't want to take supplementary classes.
Makabe-kun?
We're going to start studying
right now, Kojuurou!
Wait, what? Where are you
two going to hole up?
Stop making up weird fantasies.
Study Hall
Four-Character Kanji Compounds
Modern Literature
English Essay Training
#3 "Yoshino's Magic Show"
First, I have to find out
what you know and what you don't know.
There's no point in starting now.
How did you even get into this school?
It's apparently one of the seven wonders.
What the heck are the other six?
It really is amazing that we
ended up in the same school.
It's apparently one of the seven wonders.
What are the other six?
They're having a similar
conversation right next to us...
H-Hey, what a coincidence.
Are you two studying for a test, too?
I was just helping out Yoshino.
If the rumors are true, we'll end
up in supplementary classes.
Wait, what?
She seems like she should be smart,
but her grades are that bad?
Looks like we're in the
same boat, Koiwai-san.
Makabe-kun's teaching me, too.
Wow. I'm surprised that
you're able to teach anyone anything.
Well, I study when I need to.
I see you're as overconfident as ever,
despite falling for something so simple.
Hopefully you won't trip up again.
If you leave things to me,
you could exchange email addresses
and go on dates all you want.
If you're going to say all that,
why don't we make a wager?
Huh?
It'll be a contest.
Will it be me and Kojuurou
or you and Koiwai-san that scores
higher on the proficiency test?
If I win, go on a date with me.
M-Makabe-kun?!
Why would it even come to that?
Not feeling so confident now?
That's not the point.
Besides, what's in it for me if
I do participate in that wager?
If you win, Adagaki-san,
you can give me whatever
nickname you'd like.
Pig's Foot
I'll stick that nickname on my back
and go through high school with
it on my back until I graduate.
Well, that sounds entertaining.
But that won't be enough.
If I win, you'll have to pay for
my lunch until I say it's enough.
Fine.
Don't come crying to me later.
M-Makabe-kun, I'm not sure about this.
It'll be fine.
If what she said was true,
this won't be two against two,
but three against one.
Um, Aki-sama...
Don't you need to study?
Are you suggesting that I'd lose to Makabe?
No, but, um...
I heard that he got a perfect
score on the transfer exam.
He did?
He's apparently the first person
to do that at our school.
I thought he was just some gross
narcissist... That's why I...
Aki-sama.
I will support you all the way.
but if it comes down to it,
Guidebook
please use this.
"If it comes down to it"?
This is never going to happen!
Anyway, you just need to study!
I'll support you as much as you need.
I'm very sorry.
Koiwai Yoshino
Crap...
Come to think of it, this is the
first time I've ever called a girl.
Am I okay with Koiwai-san being my first?
But if I don't call her now, I won't be
able to talk to her about the bet.
But then again...
Incoming Call
Koiwai Yoshino
She's calling!
Sh-Should I answer?
Am I okay with giving my first time
being called by a girl to Koiwai-san?
Incoming Call
Koiwai Yoshino
Whatever! H-Hello?
You take too long to answer.
Well, as a guy, I needed to prepare myself.
Oh, so about the wager,
you'll help me out, right?
I can't.
Huh?
Even if you suddenly make
a decision like that
on your own, I have my own timing.
Wait a sec! But...
Huh? "Don't make the people live,
but don't kill them"?
Are we talking about Tokugawa Ieyasu here?
How could this... Why?!
Math Test
S-Sorry, Makabe-kun.
I'm doing my best to study,
but if all else fails,
Great General Designated Bottom
I'll have her give me an
embarrassing nickname, too.
Great General Designated Bottom
Pig's Foot
No, you don't need to go that far.
When was the Crimean War?
1853.
What kind of cell division occurs
in order for gametes to form?
Meiosis.
"I even cough alone."
Ozaki Housai.
What's the Earth's mass?
5.972 × 10^24 kilograms.
What is a way to say "Your mom
has an outie" in English?
Son of a bitch!
Right now, we're about even.
I need to put more pressure
on her, or we're in trouble.
At this point, it's going to come
down to our own abilities.
No way...
Onii-chan's actually studying
instead of working out.
Maa-kun said he has a very
important test tomorrow.
Huh...
I'm thinking about making
Maa-kun's lunch tomorrow.
It has to be low in calories,
high in protein, with no grease.
I'll go all-out and make a
character-themed lunch!
Oh, I want one, too!
Whatever. Even without Koiwai-san's help,
I just have to win tomorrow.
Well, Kojuurou, do you think you'll make it?
For now. It's all thanks to you, Makabe-kun.
All right. Now all we have left
is math in the afternoon.
I was extra attentive in teaching him math,
so we should have a good chance.
Makabe-kun, let's eat lunch.
I used my head too much, and now I'm hungry.
Sure. I'll go buy some drinks.
I'm sorry.
Huh? No, it's fine.
It was weird of me to rely on you
for a fight I decided to undertake myself.
And as a result, I got tons of studying in,
so Kojuurou and I are both in top form today.
We're not gonna lose.
Huh?
Drink that, and do your best
on the rest of the tests.
But you can't help me out, right?
Should you be cheering me on?
It doesn't matter now.
Mommy
What was that about?
Test
Math
Stay focused until the very end, all of you.
Begin!
Good. These are all questions
I anticipated. Now I can...
I think... my...
stomach hurts.
This pain... Could it be...
It doesn't matter now.
Did she actually mean...
It doesn't matter, because I made
the necessary preparations.
Is that what she meant?!
She must've put laxatives or
something in that coffee,
as an assassin for Adagaki!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Adagaki Aki and Koiwai Yoshino!
You're both my enemies after all!
How dare you do something so low just
because you can't win otherwise?!
You won't get away with this.
Makabe-kun!
Huh?
Hey!
M-Makabe-kun? Oh, my...
Did you need something from me?
Er, uh, I was looking for Adagaki-san.
Adagaki-san? She's not here today.
Huh?
Apparently she's out with a fever. Right?
Yeah.
Wait a minute...
Does that mean we had already won
by the time that happened earlier?
Then why would she give me laxatives?
Onii-chan, did you eat the
lunch that Mom made?
Messages
Sister
Edit
The eggs in the omelet
were bad. It was so sour!
That stupid old hag...
Makabe-kun, do your best in
the supplementary class!
Yeah, I will.
Supplementary Class
How am I the only one that has
to take supplementary classes?
There's a method where you
find the common factor.
It can be "x" or, as you see here,
it could be the function where
Well, I guess
the factor is inside the parentheses.
this sort of counts as a date.
Wow, look at that.
He looks so cool!
But with that look, he must be going on a date.
Huh? A date?
But didn't that wager end in a draw?
The fact that you're giving up
there is your flaw, Pig's Foot.
Don't call me Pig's Foot!
Sunday at noon.
You'll meet up at the station.
Aki-sama will definitely show up. Bye.
Hey!
If what she said on the phone was true,
then at long last...
Adagaki Aki and I...
Whoa, look at how she's dressed.
What the hell? Is that for a
part-time job or something?
Adagaki Aki is standing where
we're supposed to meet
and wearing a transformation
magical girl cosplay?
It's that one show. The anime that
used to be on Sunday mornings.
Um,
can I get a picture?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
It's really well-made!
You're cosplaying Whitening-san, right?
I-I have no idea what you're talking about.
Adagaki-san!
M-Makabe!
A-Are you all right?
Tch. 3D girls are so lame.
This is why I hate disgusting men.
I give you the nickname
"Acidic Cleanser and Rag."
"Acid Rag" for short.
The fact that it sounds less threatening
when you shorten it is frightening.
Anyway, the menace is gone now. Let's go.
You're not gonna explain
why you're dressed like that?
Huh?
Oh, dear.
You look rather experienced,
but you don't even know
the dress code for dates?
Huh?
To break the ice on the first date,
wearing a costume is a given.
That's the most basic of basic rules!
Wh-What the?
How does the Cruel Princess
end up like this,
Koiwai Yoshino?!
I guess you were the Fairy Godmother
rather than Cinderella!
I told you. Timing is important.
If you leave it to me, everything
will go according to plan.
I obey all of Aki-sama's orders.
That's why Aki-sama believes
everything I say and do.
She'll easily believe me.
So if she were to use this
servant-master relationship
against her, it'd be the ultimate deceit.
Are you listening?
Y-Yeah.
Or rather, why are you
going so far to help me?
If I stay on the line too long,
Aki-sama will get suspicious.
Oh, right.
Anyway, do your best, Pig's Foot.
Anything but that nickname, please!
At any rate, I'm going to use this date and
this derpy cosplay to my advantage!
Sorry, I guess I didn't research enough.
So there's a dress code for first dates, huh?
See? Like I said.
But I guess that means you admit
that this is a date, Adagaki-san.
A-Are you stupid?
This is all because your mental
fortitude is soft as tofu!
Huh? Me?
Because you failed your test,
you couldn't even eat,
so you burst out crying in class,
and in the nurse's office,
they caught you hiding a bunch of
wrist-cutting attempts with your sleeve.
When Yoshino told me the
whole story and said that only I
could save you since we were in
the supplementary class together,
I had no choice but to spend
a day with you! Hmph!
What the hell's the deal with this set-up
of a lovesick girl off in
fantasy land, Koiwai Yoshino?
From now on, be appreciative
of that, and live a quiet life.
Huh? Wait, you rented the place out?
Is it that surprising?
Man... I guess some things never change.
Hey.
You're too close.
Oh, of course.
Why are you so far away?!
Ugh, she's such a pain!
Man, I didn't have any
background information,
but I didn't think it'd be such a
horror in more ways than one.
What did you think, Adagaki-sa—
She's dead!
Whitening-san is dead!
Wait a moment.
Right now, some phenomenon is
occurring that's draining all strength
from my knees and preventing
me from leaving my seat.
I think you're just scared stiff.
You didn't know it was a horror movie?
Well, Yoshino planned everything.
Honestly, she's useless.
So I guess getting food is out of the question?
No, it's not!
How can she eat so much after
watching a movie like that?
Actually, stop nonchalantly pushing
your empty plates toward me.
The Cruel Princess that I know is
much stronger, more arrogant,
and at the least...
She wasn't someone who could eat enough
lunch and dessert for three people
at a family restaurant while dressed
up as someone from Hadapure.
This is just a hunch...
What?
The reason you eat so much isn't
something you were born with, right?
Well...
I think it started when something
awful happened in my past.
Something awful?
Hey, lady.
Yes?
Why are you dressed so weird?
And she gets right to the point!
I-It's not weird.
This is from I'm Hadapure.
Do you want to be Hadapure, lady?
No, no, no!
Please stop, Adagaki-san!
Listen up. I'm sure you don't understand
because you're still a child,
but this is a necessary ritual
when a man and a woman date.
"Ritual"?
Yes. In order to break the
ice on the first date,
you must wear a costu—
That's enough!
W-Wait, Makabe!
I was just getting to the good part!
I'm sorry, Adagaki-san.
I couldn't find the right
time to say it, but...
It's not normal?
To think I folded from the
stares of everyone around
rather than let a girl embarrass herself.
I see. So you don't... You don't do this.
C-Come to think of it, summer clothes
should be coming out about now.
I should check them out.
Th-That's a great idea!
Please try on your items over here.
What's wrong, Adagaki-sa—
Um, uh...
N-No!
Once upon a time, when I was
a bullied, chubby little kid,
I happened to run into a
huge mansion and met her.
You need to get stronger! How pathetic!
She didn't hold back
and was almost as hard on me
as the other bullies.
That's right.
The Cruel Princess I know is
much stronger, more arrogant...
You're so kind, Masamune.
...and just as kind.
Oh, you're awake. I'm going home, then.
Ow...
Adagaki-san...
Wh-What?
Sorry I scared you back there.
You'd better be.
That was an emotion I didn't need in my plan.
But I... I...
Wouldn't you usually say,
"No, it was my fault," there?
Why would she look so smug?
This is all for Aki-sama.
Huh? What are you talking about?
You asked me why I was
helping you, Pig's Foot.
I believe that Aki-sama needs
to reexamine herself a bit.
If you dump her, and that makes
her a little more modest,
it greatly benefits me
as well as Aki-sama.
So that's it. All right.
But planning the lap pillow
was going a bit far, wasn't it?
Lap pillow? Plan?
I totally almost fell for her.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, come on.
You can't fool me, you scheming Cinderella.
Anyway, I'm looking forward
to working with you again,
Master Koiwai.
"Master"...
It's rare for you to be talking to
someone other than Aki-sama.
Did something fun happen?
I'm having a lot of fun.